I ate seven pints of ice cream this week
and was still able to maintain a caloric
deficit. Here's how I did it. I used my
Ninja Creamy to recreate some of my
favorite ice cream flavors, but with a
fraction of the calories and double, if
not triple the protein. Here are the
seven pints I made this week. That first
one you saw was a royal strawberry
cheesecake blizzard from DQ. That one
was literally my favorite recipe I've
ever made. Now, this is a chure for
churros, which is a Ben & Jerry's
recreation. Cinnamon base with little
cinnamon sugar dusted brownie pieces.
Now, this is an absolute classic cookie
monster, which is a blue vanilla base
with Oreos mixed in and topped with some
protein cookie dough. Now, this was
another Ben & Jerry's recreation. Coffee
coffee buzz buzz buzz. An all-time
classic coffee flavored ice cream with
little dark chocolate covered espresso
beans. Then, you guys kept asking for my
vanilla base recipe, so I had to give it
to you. This is the starting point for
tons of my recipes. So, if you get this
down, you'll be able to make so many of
my recipes. The best thing about it is
that it's so low calorie, so you can add
basically whatever toppings you want.
Then I did a little Mexican chocolate
flavor. So this was a chocolate base
with some cinnamon and cayenne pepper to
give it a little spice. And then I ended
off the week by recreating Gary Queen's
Reese's Fluffer Nutter Blizzard. This is
a vanilla base with a peanut butter
swirl, peanut butter cups, and a
marshmallow fluff core. This was insane.